[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "ORGAN: Did you think one day you'd be world famous for cross- dressing?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "You know, when the votes started getting counted we knew pretty quickly we have -- you know, we have a fairly sophisticated model.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "It's all going to plan?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Were you pleased about the level of the turnout?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Look, I think the problem for the Republican Party is that the center of gravity has shifted so far to the right that they're way out of the mainstream.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "If you were putting your strategist's hat on and looking at their campaign, where do you think they really, in the end, lost it?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, I think that he certainly bears some -- people want cooperation on both sides.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "But how much of the responsibility lies with him, with Speaker Boehner, do you think?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe the economy is improving, but I want to challenge a bit of your premise because one of the reasons the economy is improving is because this president was brave.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Are you hoping you're going to get the kind of economic security if not prosperity in this term that will allow you to do perhaps the things Barack Obama, when he sailed in on hope and change, hoped he could do?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "One is, I understand that the first person the president called after knowing that he won was Bill Clinton, is that right?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question about it.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Does he feel a big debt of gratitude to him?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I know this has been the subject of a lot of discussion.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Are you a relieved man this morning?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Abused his entire life.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "He's been abused?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "How did you find this out?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "So he told you?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "You support him?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "No, I never felt that.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "So that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "I did, about four years ago I asked, why.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Every award -- and listen, that's exactly what I thought very early on.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Is that guilt, do you think?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "No, he hasn't.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Would you like him to?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "You don't know me.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes, never --", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Did you ever think when you were young and you started treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross- dressing?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "It's about strong women.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Any comment?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "-- show off about it?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, because it's -- I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "My faith.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "In that order.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "It doesn't mean that order?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I actually did.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "You've lost 30 pounds?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Mostly I worked with a trainer, a guy Anthony Golston.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "How did you do it?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Yes, you don't -- you don't eat as much and you move a lot more, and the thing that I was working out and running five miles -- this Krav Maga, Israeli fighting, and I'm tell you, I'm dropping names here, but this guy Eric down in Atlanta who worked with me was amazing at -- I did it for five minutes and couldn't get off the floor.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "But is it basically about you just don't eat as much?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Because there are --", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Once, yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I think we were both very young.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "And what went wrong?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "It was, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes, because we both were in a place where -- and I just realized I should not have said this because -- I should not have said this.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Because I said too much.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "This is a fascinating side to you, because you're being so nice about it and so honest.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Why don't you ask another question?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And what's the rush?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "But don't you want little Tylers running around?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Yes, please.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Shall we move on?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "No, I felt good.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Do you want to have a glass of water?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, I did not.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Did you have any idea who she was?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I have heard of her, but I didn't know all of that she had done.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "You've never heard of her?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "Because you supplied the plane, didn't you?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Do you believe that the candidates whoever wins the presidency should be doing more to bring in tougher gun control?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "I mean who's going to take on the gun lobby here?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "ERRY: No, no, no.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 801, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 800}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "First black bond?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "Because if you lose weight at the rate you're going, you'll be skinnier than Will Smith.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "Why should it be him?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "There's one moment I'll -- and I will probably regret it for my entire life my mother was -- on a death bed.", "docId": "121111pmt", "aSentId": 818, "question": "What would you choose?", "qSentId": 817}]